{
  "level": 3,
  "unit": 2,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "If you __________ something, you told people about it.",
          "answer": "announced"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ are the people seeking an office or honor.",
          "answer": "Candidates"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To __________ is to cause someone to believe or do something.",
          "answer": "convince"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you make __________, you make choices.",
          "answer": "decisions"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To __________ is to choose by voting.",
          "answer": "elect"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To __________ is to guess an amount.",
          "answer": "estimate"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Miguel went to City Hall to learn about his local __________.",
          "answer": "government"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you are __________, you do things for yourself.",
          "answer": "independent"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "If you __________ , you got to where you were going.",
          "answer": "arrived"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ means “came to a new country to live.”",
          "answer": "Immigrated"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ means “looked at something closely and carefully.”",
          "answer": "Inspected"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A __________ is a very short amount of time.",
          "answer": "moment"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An __________ is a chance for good things.",
          "answer": "opportunity"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ are pictures taken with a camera.",
          "answer": "Photographs"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is __________ is worth lots of money, or means a lot to someone.",
          "answer": "valuable"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ means “spoken in a very quiet voice.”",
          "answer": "Whispered"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "To __________ is to spring back after hitting something.",
          "answer": "bounce"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To __________ something is to picture it in your mind.",
          "answer": "imagine"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An __________ is a person who creates something for the first time.",
          "answer": "inventor"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An __________ is someone who watches something.",
          "answer": "observer"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ occurs when several words or syllables in a row start with the same sound.",
          "answer": "Alliteration"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "In a __________ poem, the lines do not need to rhyme.",
          "answer": "free verse"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A __________ is a funny poem of five lines with a specific rhyme pattern.",
          "answer": "limerick"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Kite and sight __________ because they end with the same sound.",
          "answer": "rhyme"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
